[{"answer": " So, let me tell you about this really interesting article I read in a magazine today", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Which magazine", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 13, "question": " So, let me tell you about this really interesting article I read in a magazine today", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I dont remember.  It was at the waiting room of the dentists office that I went t", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Which magazine", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": "So, what are they?  Isnt that big pyramid in Egypt one of them", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 18, "question": " I dont remember.  It was at the waiting room of the dentists office that I went t", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Oh, ok", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 27, "question": "So, what are they?  Isnt that big pyramid in Egypt one of them", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Anyways, the article was about the 7 wonders of the world.  Do you know wha", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Oh, ok", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " You know I always here about them and Im sure I studied about them i", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Anyways, the article was about the 7 wonders of the world.  Do you know wha", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Well, theyre all from the ancient world.  You know, the times of the Egyptians", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 34, "question": " You know I always here about them and Im sure I studied about them i", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Yes.  Theres the Great Pyramid, the Hanging Gardens of Babylon, th", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Well, theyre all from the ancient world.  You know, the times of the Egyptians", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Good memory.  I recognize the first two, but Im not sure about the other ones", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Yes.  Theres the Great Pyramid, the Hanging Gardens of Babylon, th", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Yeah, theyre not really known today", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Good memory.  I recognize the first two, but Im not sure about the other ones", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Well, that sounds like an interesting article", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Yeah, theyre not really known today", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " But thats not even the interesting part.  The article said that the 7 wonders wer", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Well, that sounds like an interesting article", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 48, "question": " But thats not even the interesting part.  The article said that the 7 wonders wer", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Yep.  It was really cool.  The writers of this article decided to have a ne", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Thats cool.  How did they pick them?  How many were there", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yep.  It was really cool.  The writers of this article decided to have a ne", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " They stuck to the same number  7.  They did an online survey and people fro", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Thats cool.  How did they pick them?  How many were there", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " What were the results", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 58, "question": " They stuck to the same number  7.  They did an online survey and people fro", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " I think youll recognize a lot more of these.  They are the Great Wall of China", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 59, "question": " What were the results", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Hey.  Ive visited some of those places", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 64, "question": " I think youll recognize a lot more of these.  They are the Great Wall of China", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Me too", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Hey.  Ive visited some of those places", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " But what about the last three?  I dont know those.  What are they", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Me too", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Chichen Itza is an ancient Mayan temple city", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 67, "question": " But what about the last three?  I dont know those.  What are they", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Oh yeah.  Ive read about that", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Chichen Itza is an ancient Mayan temple city", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Machu Pichu is another ancient city, except the Incas lived there", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Oh yeah.  Ive read about that", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Ok.  Its in ruins now though, right", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Machu Pichu is another ancient city, except the Incas lived there", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Yeah.  It was abandoned hundreds of years ago.  And Petra in an ancient city i", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Ok.  Its in ruins now though, right", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Id love to see that place.  Ive never even heard about it", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Yeah.  It was abandoned hundreds of years ago.  And Petra in an ancient city i", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " I know.  Me neither.  So that was the article.  It was about the updated 7 wonder", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Id love to see that place.  Ive never even heard about it", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " That is very interesting", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 82, "question": " I know.  Me neither.  So that was the article.  It was about the updated 7 wonder", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Hey, we should plan a trip around the world to go visit all of the places", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 83, "question": " That is very interesting", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Everyone should see the 7 wonders of the world before they die, right", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Hey, we should plan a trip around the world to go visit all of the places", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Thats right", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Everyone should see the 7 wonders of the world before they die, right", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Well have to start saving", "docId": "09-08", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Thats right", "qSentId": 85}]
